Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 5
I'm going to pick up Unni and go with her.
You're completely done for! Your father is very upset at you.
I said I get it.
I know..but instead of going home alone, making Unni go in front of me is better
so that's what I'm going to do.
Hang up, Uncle..
Son Sang Gi Exhibition
Why are you here?
I came here to see the paintings.
Did you come without knowing what this was, Unni? I came here knowing about the exhibit.
Did you not know?
Oppa Gi Hoon told me.
What did you say?
Didn't you know?
We're dating.
Oppa Gi Hoon... and me.
Why? Do you think I'm lying?
Excuse me, was this painting in the catalog?
Yes, it was.
Really? I didn't see it.
I'll show it to you.
Did you not know Oppa and I were dating?
Maybe Oppa doesn't contact you at all..
She would want to ask me,
She would very much like to ask me,
but this annoying sister is pretending to sleep.
If she would just ask me, I could answer her in a second,
but nothing is easy for her when it comes to me.
I have something to say to you, before going home..
I used my credit card so much, Father is angry. Can you calm him down for me?
What?
Can you help stop Dad?
How much did you spend?
I don't know. Just a lot.
At the end, I couldn't use it because I exceeded the limit.
What were you doing that you had to spend so much money?
There are so many pretty things in this world.
You exceeded your credit buying pretty things?
I didn't just buy things for myself. I bought things for Mom and you-
Forget it.
I have no interest in picking up after your crazy acts.
Just go.
What's so great about you that you always act like you're better than others?
I also have a thing called circumstances.
Hey..stop right there!
Can't you hear someone speaking to you?
- Let go of me before you speak.
- Dad is waiting with the wooden rod.
Are you going to let me get hit?
-What is your dream?
-What?
How do you plan on living the rest of your life?
Do you have anything like a strategy or plan of action?
If I have one, are you curious about even that?
Are you asking because you're curious? You're not right?!
It's another boast of yours you say when you try to step on me and it's like an introduction of what you're going to say later, right?
Your introductions when you first hear it, you don't feel anything, but when you think about it after the matter,
you feel quite horrible.
Did you know that?
You must know.
You're saying those things intentionally to make me feel bad. There's no reason you wouldn't know.
Do you want to keep doing ballet?
Of course. Do you think I'm crazy, going to auditions every day for something I don't want to do?
Then why do you get eliminated?
Why can you never pass the audition?
Even if you were okay, shouldn't you have passed at least one audition by now?
Hey. Do you think there are hundreds and thousands of ballet groups in our country?
Do you even practice?
- Do you practice until you feel you'll die?
- Of course!
Then why are you feet so clean and pretty?
-What?
- The toenails fall off countless times for those who practice endlessly
and their bones stick out constantly making it seem like the foot of an animal.
Why do your feet look like feet that have never even been blistered before?
You don't practice right? You don't want to do ballet too right?
You don't have a dream, do you? You don't have a strategy or plan or action. You have no thoughts at all.
Just say you have no thoughts.
Then I'll understand your boring life as the life of a poor kid who had nothing better to do than swipe their card,
and help you, whether that is to hide the wooden rod or break it.
Is that all you are going to say?
Don't cry in front of mel ... it's annoying.
Hyo Seon is here.
- What are you up to, you punk?
Father!
Dad... I did wrong. I won't do it again.
Stand up.
Father..I said I'm sorry,
Stand up!
-Honey, Honey, Honey!!!
You let go of this and leave.
- Hyo Seon, hurry up and leave.
- Where are you going!
Hit me. I did wrong, Honey, okay?
Won't you move?
Hyo Seon, hurry up and leave!
Hey! Hyo Seon! Won't you get back here?
Give this to me.
-Do you want to see me die?
- What??
Rather than see her calves bruised so purple,
I'd prefer dying.
This isn't something to cover up for her. What is she doing outside?
Hyo Seon, won't you get back here right this instant?
I'll do it. Let me do it.
Why would you hit a pretty kid that we never get to see?
If Hyo Seon's calves get bruised, I think I'll become sick.
After I gave birth to Joon Soo, when I am sick now and lie down,
I don't think I'll be able to get up.
If I get sick, would you like it?
Do you... want to become widower twice?
I'll talk to her about it.
I've tried before, but I felt bad about her being dropped off in Seoul all by herself.
My heart hurt every time I saw her...
I told her to do whatever she wanted,
so I'm also at fault.
Even using the cards indiscriminately is a problem
but what she does. It's often she doesn't come home until its past midnight.
What did you say? After midnight?
She's older now, so it should be a given that she has a boyfriend or two,
but I feel like maybe she's meeting more than just one or two...
-What?!!
- Honey, please don't yell..
How can a girl just be diligent all the time?
She spent a night out? More than one or two men?
Wait a minute. This little-!
If you do that, it'll seem like I snitched on her.
Don't be like that, and listen to me.
This type of talk is better if the mom does it, not the dad.
Don't you think so?
Do you think I have the right to be Hyo Seon's mother?
Is that even a question?
If you hold the wooden rod to her again,
then I'll understand it as you not acknowledging me as her mom and pack up my things.
I'll take care of it. I'll put her in place.
Let me do that, Honey.
How many tails do you have? You, Goodness ...
What do you mean, tails?
I only have 9.
Goodness...
You little...
♫ In the solitude which wakes me up  ♫
♫ when I wake up from an exhausted sleep
♫
Did you really not know I was dating him?
I guess he doesn't contact you at all.
♫ I'm secretly smiling ♫
♫ Love leaves again this way ♫
♫ When the beautiful season arrives ♫
♫ In the sadness you left in the longing ♫
♫ I walk this street again ♫
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear, ah ♫
♫ I can't bear it ♫
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
For some reason I did think that one day
you would leave somewhere.
I know you aren't meeting Gi Hoon anymore,
and unfortunately,
I know neither this house nor myself
must be great consolidation for you.
When Gi Hoon left, I was the most worried about you.
Let me leave.
I want to leave.
I can't let you do that.
I'm going to leave.
If you don't let me leave now,
I'm going to leave on my way to school or sneak out early in the morning.
I'm going to leave someday.
I know.
When I feel like I can let you leave and not worry about you, I'll let you go.
I promise.
I always keep the promises I make.
Will you believe that I'm worried about you?
Can you believe
that I will keep my promise?
For the time being, I'll be a good reason for you to stay here.
Believe me.
The conclusion I've reached
is that I want to pick someone.
I want to select someone who is familiar with marketing and train them until I can trust them to take care of things,
then I want to go into research.
There's more than just one or two things you can research about on yeast.
Do you think a young person, and a smart one at that, would come work in a countryside?
Eat up, you two.
Talk about business elsewhere.
I have no interest in making it so large.
There's a lot of things that go into just building a simple factory like this.
- Then what will I do?
- What?
You're going to use me with no intent of growing your business?
How are you going to use me?
Did you have me study microbiology only to have me run errands for you?
You don't need knowledge in biochemistry to disinfect a jar.
Uh...Nothing is fun,
Who is it?
Mom!!
- Where is it?
- Huh?
I saw your credit card use history. It said you bought a bag. What else did you buy?
You must have every season's release!
I bought one for you, too.
Really?
I hid it in the car in case Dad finds out.
Should I bring it right now?
- This is for you, Mom.
- Ah!! It's so pretty!!
It's so pretty right? The moment I saw this, I thought of you.
But, do you think I have clothes that will go with this?
Then should we go shopping for your clothes?
Shall we?
- Let's do that.
- It's so pretty.
Are these all yours?
Wow, this one is super pretty!
It's super pretty, right?
But this one is so large that you won't look good with it.
What?
Wait a minute..
Hey! This looks like for old people, I should use this!
Yes, you use it, Mom!
Right?!
We must really be mother and daughter, judging from our similar preferences.
Can you bring me the red one? And the black one next to it?
Okay! What about the green one?
Are you crazy?
What am I supposed to do if you come here at night?
Hello?
Where are you right now?
You're going to come in?
Right now, at this time of day?
Hyo Seon, did I do something wrong?
If I did, tell me.
I told you that you didn't do anything wrong!
- Then why are you suddenly not picking up my calls?
- This is driving me crazy!
Hyo Seon, do you think I came here all the way from Seoul for you to act so coldly to me?
Speak to me nicely.
Okay, I'll do that.
Oppa Hyeon Gu, you should go back to Seoul today.
Drive safely, okay?
Oppa, why?
What? Your tire is flat?
What does that have to do with m-
Do you think you can get to a repair shop?
There's a new car center in that area, so go there.
♫ Again today my memory led me astray ♫
♫ I who am strolling at the end of the street ♫
♫ where you can't hold me again ♫
Isn't there something wrong with her sense of pain?
♫ I ask again about the way. ♫
♫ Saying I want to see you and hold you again ♫
♫ While looking at heaven I'm praying ♫
♫ It must be you. ♫
♫ I cannot be without you. ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫
♫ because you are the only one I love. ♫
Come here, and sit..
Has it been 7 years?
It's been eight years.
Have you been doing well?
Why have you become this old?
Gi Jeong is doing well.
He's a wise one.
- Congratulations, Mr. Byun.
- Yes?
I heard your youngest son will be attending Georgia Tech starting this spring.
How did you...
I want to give you a small present. Can you spare me some time?
- Make some time in my schedule.
- Yes, sir.
His own people are a given,
but he even takes detailed care of all my employees as well.
It hasn't been long since your knee surgery. Have you rested enough?
What?
Oh, yes.
Now, I have nobody left.
Shareholders
This is what you mentioned during our last call.
There's a more important problem than this..
That's why I called you,
New Wave In The Domestic Makgeolli Market
Daeseong True Family Quickly Increasing Marketshare
Hello, Ahjushi
Yes, it's Gi Hoon.
Yeah it's the quiet Gi Hoon.
Yes, that goblin-like Gi Hoon.
Have you been well?
Face!
Eyes.
Nose.
- Hair!
- Ouch!
This is our house! Fuck off!
Why! Let's play! Come on, let's play!
No! I'm not going to play with you!
Mommy!
You..do you live in this house?
Hm? Do you live in this house?
Who the heck are you?
Victory!
I'm Han Jeong Woo, the person who's been calling for a job for six months now.
Okay, I understand you're Han Jeong Woo, so stop yelling!
Yes, I'll fix it.
- Follow me.
- Yes, I understand!
- Stop yelling!
- Okay, I understand.
Please come this way.
Here is our next stop.
The next place you need to see is the place where using traditional methods, we were able to produce the makgeolli of today.
I was going to have you greet the boss, but I guess you can't right now.
You wait a bit, okay?
The soy bean paste you saw earlier, we can make sure the taste is preserved properly.
Aftter the alcohol is distilled or made in the factory here,
the alcoholic beverages produced will go through different distribution processes.
We receive special orders,
and we are focusing on the beverages delivered to five star hotels.
Next, I will guide you to the fermentation room. This way please.
Yes, let's go.
Please head this way.
Would you please hold your breath briefly?
Do you hear the smell of alcohol breathing?
Oh, I really do hear something.
Is this the sound of it being fermented?
Yes, that's right.
If you place your ear up to the jars,
but don't hear this sound, we toss all the alcohol away.
Oh, I see.
Be quiet for a moment. Let me listen to it again.
There's another place we ferment our foods.
Let's head over there.
That's so cool.
Come here this way, please,
Let's go..
National Ballet Company Audition
That's all. Good work.
I'll try again.
I said good work. You don't need to try again.
Ms. Goo Hyo Seon, you can stop!
Ms. Goo Hyo Seon, what are you doing?
-I'll do it again!
- 𝙒𝙝𝙖𝙩 𝙞𝙨 𝙮𝙤𝙪𝙧 𝙙𝙧𝙚𝙖𝙢?
You may stop now!
What are your plans for the future?
Do you have anything like a strategy or a plan of action?
I can start making a plan from now.
- What in the world is she saying?
- I can start making a plan now.
I don't think she has the basics. Why is she saying those things?
She shouldn't have even started doing ballet at all.
2010 National Ballet Company Audition
Do you know what an audition is?
Yes, an audition.
I follower my daughter to an audition for a ballet company.
Do I look like I have loads of free time to you?
As I said to you before, today's not a good day..
-Well, today's different than any other day!
-Mom!
-Why?
-Huh? About what?
- What?
Did you fight with someone?
Oh, was it with Unni?
Oh... sure.
How did it go? Did you do well?
- I did well ... not making any mistakes,
-Mm, that's good, it's good.
Good job. As long as you didn't make any mistakes.
Let's go..let's go,
Mom. If I don't pass this audition,
then I might just go back down and wipe jars.
You can't do that! A person needs to have dreams.
Why would you waste away just cleaning jars?
There are plenty of people who can wipe jars even if you don't.
Huh?
If you haven't found anyone special, I found someone who's just right. I think it'd nice to work with him.
Two people are coming for an interview tomorrow.
Really?
In order to have them make a decision after seeing the atmosphere here,
I thought it would be best to conduct the interview here, so I convinced them to come down.
Then he can do it as well. The interview.
- Who is it?
- See and judge for yourself,
You ... are you sleeping these days?
What?
It looks like you aren't sleeping these days,
It's not that I'm not sleeping at all. I sleep enough to get by.
Why are you doing that?
I didn't ask you to help me so you could live a youth-less life.
I'm not just helping you to be helpful.
What?
I'm waiting.
Waiting for what?
You said you would let me go once you were certain you wouldn't worry about me no matter where I go.
I know you said that just to hold on to me for the time being.
But... I trust that you'll keep your promise.
If I succeed inthe research of fermentation which I'm conducting now, I'm going to leave.
- How—
- If I just succeed,
then I'll consider all my debt to you as paid off.
How can you think of that as debt?
How could you really—
I mean, how can you—
I have to go to the factory.
If you're not coming with me, I'll go alone.
You should go first.
I kept my promise.
Don't you know me?
Gi Hoon?
I see you recognize me.
Oppa!
I don't.
You must have the wrong person.
Hey—
That woman...
It's me, Jeong Woo!
You must have the wrong person.
Hyo Seon's uncle...
you're the new employee Mr. Yang brought, right?
Are you perhaps looking for Hyo Seon? She's at home right now.
I'll let her know someone's looking for her.
It's me, Jeong Woo!
The Jeong Woo who you used to live together with hairy ahjusshi Jang.
You remember now, right? The Jeong Woo whom you cooked for.
You're a familiar face.
You're Hyo Seon's older sister, right?
Do you remember me?
Unni.
Don't you know Oppa Gi Hoon?
Hello.
Yes.
Dad's in his office, right?
Let's go, Oppa.
I'm calling you because it's past the interview time.
Are the roads very congested?
I'm sorry. I've got a job somewhere else.
I understand. Congratulations.
Both of them aren't coming to the interview?
Then, shall we look at the next interviewee?
Have you been to the military?
Me?
Who else is here right now?
I have. Why?
Where? Public Services?
I was a marine.
Which class?
Class 921.
Sir! I am Han Jeong Woo from Class 1065.
At ease.
Head in.
You have incredible work experiences in Seoul.
Why are you trying to work in this countryside?
Are you just staying here temporarily until you get a better position?
That isn't the case.
I will do my work so well that you won't want me to leave.
If you suspect I'm about to leave, you'll treat me even better.
I've lived here before and like it here.
The best part of working here is that I have a place to stay and food to eat.
I don't know if you're aware of this, but I don't have anywhere else to go.
Did you study abroad as soon as you returned from your military service?
Yes.
Did it take a long time for you to earn your degree?
You were in the States for five and a half years.
After I got my degree, I worked as an intern at a marketing firm in New York.
During all that time, did you never come to Korea?
Every break, I came to Korea.
You did? You came here every break?
You horrible punk. You never even called.
I'm sorry.
I was busy every time I came.
Hello?
I'm Goo Hyo Seon, who recently auditioned.
Yes, I understand.
Goodbye.
What are your dreams?
Did you not pass?
Are you upset?
So much that I can't speak.
It's okay.
If you keep failing, one day you'll pass.
But who cares if you don't pass?
There are so many fun things to do in this world.
My Oppa
where were you that you're here only now?
What?
Oppa,
I'm so happy to see you.
Why are you being like that? Why are you about to cry?
I have no dreams and no strategy
and no plans.
Can someone like me live a fun life, too?
Tell me something I can believe just like I can believe that the moon is square, Oppa.
If you live, you'll find a dream,
a strategy, and a plan.
The order doesn't have to be a certain way.
My Oppa...
Have you been well, little kid?
Why are you here only now?
You bad punk...
A television advertisement is the best idea,
but given our financial situation, it might be too much for us to do.
Just like the way of a TV advertisement
After referencing each PR firm's marketing strategy, I am giving this presentation.
Here's an example of Osangju liquor
Osangju has a beer company Osang Beer, Hong Liquors as a specialist in light makgeolli and
additionally 6 subsidiary companies. It is the leading market player.
When Osangju released Osang fresh draft beer, the method they employed for PR was--
Wait a minute.
How much would a TV advertisement cost?
What?
Compare the costs of a television advertisement
to how much time and costs would go into placing 10 posters in every bar in the country.
Calculate the costs and submit a report.
I need to head to the factory, so I'll leave first.
The inspection team said they would check our factories one more time.
Try lifting that.
- This?
- Drink it from the bottle with the label facing out.
If you're making me do this for no good reason, know that you're so dead.
It's so good!
Unni, do you want some too?
What are you doing right now?
You're quite pretty.
What?
Huh?
What did you say to me?
Say it again. Say it one more time.
What?
You said I was pretty, right?
You said I'm pretty
with your own mouth.
It's not the first time you're hearing that.
Mother calls you pretty at least a few hundred times a day,
and all our family members could die for you, they love you so much.
Joon Soo says you're prettier than me, too.
Your boyfriend probably thinks the same.
Stop pestering me and go home. I need to work.
TV CF Filming Costs
These are the costs of a TV advertisement and putting up posters in every bar.
Re-print it.
Redo it. We don't need an advertisement agency.
Are you going to place an TV ad without an advertising agency?
We don't need a model or, what is that called?
We don't need a content or scenario writer, either.
Just calculate the costs of filming and broadcasting it. Oh, and-
the production team should be the best at what they do.
Make sure to be generous with the funds for that. Same with the poster.
Other than that, try to reduce costs as much as possible in your report.
Do you have anything else to say?
Nope. Please leave.
Do you really not have anything to say?
You really don't?
I understand. I'll leave now.
- Where are we going right now?
- Just be quiet.
Okay. I understand.
- Get out.
- What?
Get out and wait.
What?
I said get out and wait. Call me if even an ant lingers around the area.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Get in.
We're going to take Hyo Seon to Do Ga and have her work there.
Eun Jo, you take care of her.
Dad!
- I heard you failed the national ballet club audition.
You fail every audition.
Are you even skilled at ballet?
There isn't much that Hyo Seon can do.
Look for something.
If you and I work together, we'll be able to find something for her to do.
Darling, Eun Jo is enough.
How can someone so young endure here?
She has to play in wide waters to see the world with broad eyes.
You need to have a broad outlook on life to do big things.
I insisted that was true, but he still placed her there.
With the excuse of taking care of the errands in Seoul, I came here
and snuck out to see you, even if it was just for a little bit.
Now, that's all done for.
Drink up. This is our last today.
Who are you to decide this is our last?
That's true. We've had too many lasts, right?
- Kang Soo Ah.
- What?
You should stop working and come back to me.
How can you say something like that? Know your place.
Do you think I hang out with you because I like you?
I've told you hundreds of thousands of times.
I'm only doing this because I think I'll die
if I don't let my stuffy heart breathe freely at least once each month.
- Do you have to speak that way? (Using informal speech)
- How can you address me as you!
I'm someone who's officially married and has a son
with someone who is the CEO of a company.
I'm the wife of a household, that no longer has to be chased around by others.
Do you think I'm the same as someone like you?
I don't even know why you smile when you smile,
or why you're angry when you get angry.
I just don't know anything.
Why are you out here?
Hyo Seon's friends called me,
saying that she drank and passed out somewhere.
Eun Jo and Gi Hoon went to get her.
That little punk really...
Honey, I just met with Hyo Seon's friend because of Hyo Seon.
Let's go inside.
This is Kyung Wha Chung.
Don't you remember anything?
Do you really..
not have anything to say to me?
Do you really not have a single thing to say to me?
You bad wretch.
I don't understand a single thing you're saying.
You horrible girl... How could you act like you don't know me?
Do I have to act like I know you?
- Do you know how much I -
- Shut up.
What?
You crazy bastard.
Whatever I am, or whatever Hyo Seon is,
I didn't know you were a bastard, but you are.
What the hell...
That's not it.
- No?
- It's not Hyo Seon.
Really?
It's not. That's not the truth.
Does Hyo Seon also think that's not the truth?
It's not.
I'm telling you it's not the truth!
What right do you have?
You're fired.
Don't take a single step into this household.
Hey.
Hey!
Eun Jo.
Eun Jo...
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I cannot be without you ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
Don't give me your feelings.
I'm a bitch
If you do get a chance to get a hand of it. Please give it to me.
I feel like everything will be taken from me.
It's loyalty to the one who is feeding me.
What's going on with you?
I wish you would just die!
Do you even like Hyo Seon's dad?
♫ Wherever you are ♫
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫